I'm Peppa Pig
This is my
little brother George
This is Mummy Pig
And this
is Daddy Pig
Peppa Pig
Super Potato
Today
Mr Potato has
come to Peppa's playgroup
Children
Mr Potato is here
to talk to you today
about eating
fruit and vegetables
I am going to
show you a movie called Super Potato
Yay
Super Potato
Oh，my hat
is blown off
Help me
super potato
By the power
of vegetables
I am here
Thank you
super potato
Remember，kids
always eat
your five a day
Fruit and
vegetables keep us alive
Always remember
to eat your five
And now
we have a very
special guest
Can you
guess who it is？
It's not my daddy
is it？
No
It's not my daddy
is it？
No，it is
nobody's daddy
Is it my
mummy then？
No，it is no
relation of anyone here
The special guest
coming to see you today is…
Super
Potato is coming
Hooray
But before he does
we must call him
Super Potato
Very good
I'll just go and
see if he's outside
Keep shouting
Super potato
super potato
By the power
of vegetables
I am here
Great
Wonderful，Now
who has a question they would like to ask Super Potato？
Ask me anything
you like about fruit and vegetables
Anything
What is the tallest building you've ever jumped？
What's that？
Why do I like
carrots so much？
I'll tell you why
Because they
are so tasty
Can you run
faster than a train？
Which vegetable
makes you run fast？
That's a
good question
I would
have to say…
a Brussels sprout
Have you ever
eaten a potato？
Uh…
fruit and
vegetables keep us alive
Always remember
to eat your five
Doctors now
recommend you eat seven a day
Uh…
always remember
to eat your seven
Right
Let's all give
Super Potato a nice big clap
For coming to
see us today
Thank you
thank you
and remember，kids
eat fruit
and vegetables
Super Potato has
left the building
Oh dear
did I miss him？
Yes
He was brilliant
Well，it was
lovely to see you all
but I'd
better be going too
Bye
Come on，children
let's wave Mr
Potato goodbye
Oh dear
Mr Potato's
car won't start
Ah
I cannot get out
Mr Potato is stuck
Help，let me out
What shall we do？
Help，help
Call for Super Potato
Super Potato
I think he might
be too busy to come
Super Potato，Super
There
it didn't work
Now I
think we need…
What's that
in the sky？
Is it a bird？
Is it a plane？
No，it's a potato
By the power
of vegetables
I am here
Super Potato has
come to the rescue
Using my super
vegetable vision
I can see that my
friend here is in trouble
Yes，you have
to get him out
I will use my
fruity strength
To lift
this roof off
Super Potato has
rescued Mr Potato
Yay，And
remember， kids
when trouble calls
Eat your fruits
and vegetables
Fruits and
vegetables keep us alive
Always remember
to eat your five
seven
Always remember
to eat your p7
Apple，s，oranges
bananas arrive
Eat them all as
part of your p7
Wiggle your
hips and do a jive
Always remember
to eat your p7